Hey, how you doing?
I'm Eddie.
Nice to meet you.
The question is, immigration is good for America, right?
Overall.
If you look at the net positives to things like
our society, our culture, our food, our economy,
our general diversity.
I know the D word is a bad word in places like this.
I think immigrants have been a net positive.
I think if you look at your everyday lives,
we all benefit from immigration.
And what kind of conservatives disagree with that?
The guys, some of the guys who told me to leave this place
and go back to, you know, I'm not a citizen.
Do you think all conservatives?
No.
No, in fact, Ronald Reagan, who is a president
I wasn't a big fan of until Donald Trump came along.
Now people like Reagan look good in comparison.
Reagan said in 1986, our country is a nation of immigrants.
Our immigrant heritage is our strength.
He gave an amnesty to 3 million undocumented migrants.
He understood the value of immigration.
So I'm with Reagan.
Although this guy is putting his thumb down there.
So Reagan's not popular in right wing crowds these days.
Well, he's popular with me.
Good to hear.
I'm a deferred action of childhood arrivals.
Actually, I was an illegal immigrant myself.
I came here when I was 10.
I'm what you would call a legal alien now.
I didn't have any say on my parents, you know, choices.
Yes.
Do I think that they were well-meaning
by wanting to bring me over for a better future?
Absolutely.
I believe that.
Yeah.
Did they break law?
Yes.
Do I agree with people breaking the law?